Guide to the Poly Archives Serial Publications Collection RG.030
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Poly Archives Serial Publications Collection
1884-2014
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
RG.030
32
69 Linear Feet (11 boxes and approximately 250 bound volumes)
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research without restrictions.
Arrangement
The series are arranged alphabetically by publication title.
Biographical / Historical
The serial publications in this collection were loosely grouped together in the archives in the mid 2000s. Historical notes at the series level provide an explanation of each publication in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The publications in this collection include newsletters, bulletins, newspapers, department news, yearbooks, alumni magazines and literary journals. Collectively, these publications produced by Polytechnic students, faculty, alumni, and the administration, cover over 100 years of research, innovation, and campus life.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
Newspapers; Serials (publications); Newsletters; Yearbooks; Polytechnic University (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.); Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn; Polytechnic Institute of New York
- Series I: Bohican, 11805
  Biographical / Historical
  Bohican was the student newspaper for the Farmingdale campus.
  - Volume 2, Issues 1-2, 1982; 11846 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Volume 2, Issues 3-5, 1982; 11847 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Volume 3, Issues 2-3, 1982; 11848 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Volume 4, Issues 1-3, 1983-1984; 11849 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Volume 5, Issue 1, 1984; 11850 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Volume 9, Issue 4, 1988; 11851 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Volume 10, Issue 4, 1989; 11852 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Volume 11, Issues 3-4, 1990; 11853 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Volume 14, Issues 1-2, 1993; 11854 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Volume 14, Issue 3, 1993; 11855 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Volume 15, Issue 1-3, 1993; 11856 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Series II: Cable, 11803
  Cable replaced Polygraphs as the alumni magazine in 1973. It is still published today.
  - Cable Index 1974-2008, 11857 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - June 1973 - October/November 1973, 11858 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - January/February 1974, 11859 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - October 1974, 11860 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - December 1974, 11861 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - March 1975 - April/May 1975, 11862 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - June/July 1975 - September 1975, 11863 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - November 1975, 11864 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - January 1976 - April 1976, 11865 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - July 1976 - September 1976, 11866 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - November 1976, 11867 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - February 1977 - May 1977, 11868 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - November 1977, 11869 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - February 1978 - May 1978, 11870 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - September 1978 - November 1978, 11871 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - February 1979 - May 1979, 11872 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - September 1979 - November 1979, 11873 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - February 1980 - May 1980, 11874 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - September 1980 - December 1980, 11875 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - March 1981 - June 1981, 11876 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - September 1981, 11877 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Winter 1982 - Spring/Summer 1982, 11878 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fall 1982, 11879 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Winter/Spring 1983 - Summer 1983, 11880 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Spring 1984 - Summer 1984, 11881 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Fall 1984 - Winter 1984, 11882 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Spring 1985 - Summer 1985, 11883 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Fall 1985 - Winter 1985, 11884 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Spring 1986 - Summer 1986, 11885 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Fall 1986 - Winter 1986, 11886 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Spring 1987 - Summer 1987, 11887 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Fall 1987, 11888 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Summer 1988 - Fall 1988, 11889 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Spring 1988 - Winter 1988, 11890 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Winter 1989 - Spring 1989, 11891 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Summer 1989 - Fall 1989, 11902 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Winter 1990- Spring 1990, 11903 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Summer 1990 - Fall 1990, 11904 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Spring 1991 - Summer 1991, 11905 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fall 1991, 11906 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Summer 1992 - Fall 1992, 11907 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Winter 1992 - Spring 1992, 11908 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Winter 1993 - Spring 1993, 11909 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Summer 1993 - Fall 1993, 11910 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Winter 1994 - Spring 1994, 11911 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Summer 1994 - Fall 1994, 11912 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Winter 1995 - Spring 1995, 11913 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Summer 1995 - Fall 1995, 11914 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Winter 1996 - Spring 1996, 11915 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Summer 1996 - Fall 1996, 11928 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Winter 1997 - Spring 1997, 11929 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - September 1997 - December 1997, 11930 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Spring 1998 - Summer 1998, 11931 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Fall 1998 - Winter 1998/1999, 11932 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Spring 1999 - Summer 1999, 11933 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fall 1999, 11934 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Winter 1999/2000, 11935 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Summer 2000, 11936 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Winter 2000/2001, 11937 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Spring 2001, 11938 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Summer 2001, 11954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fall 2001, 11939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Winter 2002, 11940 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Spring 2002, 11955 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Summer 2002, 11941 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fall 2002, 11956 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Winter 2003, 11942 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Spring 2003, 11957 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Summer 2003, 11943 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fall 2003, 11958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Winter 2004, 11944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Spring 2004, 11959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Summer 2004, 11945 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fall 2004, 11960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Winter 2005, 11946 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Spring 2005, 11961 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Summer 2005, 11947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fall 2005, 11962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Winter 2006, 11948 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Spring 2006, 11963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Summer 2006, 11949 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Fall 2006, 11964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Winter 2007, 11950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Spring 2007, 11965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Summer 2007, 11951 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fall 2007, 11966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Winter 2008, 11952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Spring 2008, 11967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Summer 2008, 11953 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Fall 2008, 11968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Spring 2009, 11969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Summer 2009, 11970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Fall 2009, 11971 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Spring 2010, 11972 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Summer 2010, 11973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Winter 2010, 11974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Spring 2011, 11975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Summer 2011, 11978
  - Fall 2011, 11976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Winter 2011, 11977 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Spring 2012, 11979 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Summer 2012, 11980
  - Fall 2012, 11981 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Spring 2013, 11982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Fall 2013, 11983 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Winter 2013, 11984
  - Spring 2014, 11985
  - Fall 2014, 14814 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Polycable/Polygraph notes, 1975 March; 11986 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Polycable/Polygraph notes, 1975 April-May; 11987 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Polycable/Polygraph notes, 1976 January; 11988 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Polycable/Polygraph notes, 1976 April; 11989 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Series III: Counterweight Quarterly, 11804
  Counterweight Quarterly was the student literary magazine from 1957-2002.
  - Volume 1, No. 1, 1957; 11990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Volume 2, No. 1, 1957; 11991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Volume 5, 1961; 11992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Volume 6, 1962; 11993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Volume 7 - Volume 8, 1963-1964; 11994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Volume 9, No. 1 - Volume 9, No.2, 1965-1966; 11995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Volume 9, No. 3 - Volume 9, No.4, 1966; 11996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Volume 10, No. 1 - Volume 10, No.2, 1966-1967; 11997 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Volume 10, No. 3- Volume, No.4, 1967; 11998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Volume 11, No. 1 - Volume 11, No.2, 1967-1968; 11999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Volume 11, No.3 - Volume 11, No.4, 1968; 12001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Volume 12, No. 1, 1968; 12000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Volume 12, No. 3 - Volume 12, No. 4, 1969; 12002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Volume 26, Winter - Spring 1970, 1969-1970; 12003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Volume 28, Winter - 1972, 1971-1972; 12004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fall 1996 - Spring 1997, 1996-1997; 12005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Winter 1998, 12006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Spring 2002, 12014 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Counterweight Quarterly, Vol 10, 1966-1967 (bound), 12015 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Counterweight Quarterly, Vol 1, 1967-1968 (bound), 12016 (Box 5, Item 2)
- Series IV: Feedback, 11808
  Feedback was a publication of the undergraduate Electrical Engineering department during the 1960s. In 2002, Feedback was resurrected as "IEEE Feedback, The Poly Magazine for Student Research & Much More..." sponsored by the Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE) Department with contributions by ECE and IEEE students.
  - Special Issue- Weber Interview, 1967 May; 12032 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - March 1967 - November 1967, 12033 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - December 1967 - May 1968, 1967-1968; 12034 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - February 1970 - May 1976, 1970-1976; 12035 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fall 2002, 12036 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Series V: Fusion, 11806
  Fusion was a student newspaper owned and published by Polytechnic University. Fusion's office was on the Farmingdale campus and the paper was distributed to both Long Island and Brooklyn campuses. All Poly students were invited to submit articles for publication through the Farmingdale Student Life office or to become a member of the Fusion staff.
  Fusion was re-inaugurated in 2004 as a magazine staffed by students of Polytechnic University and funded by the Department of Technical Communications. The new iteration of the magazine focused on engineering and technology articles as well as social issues important to engineering students and professionals.
  - Volume 1, No. 1-3, 1994; 12037 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Volume 1, No. 4-5, 1995; 12038 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Volume 2, No. 2-3, 1995; 12039 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Volume 2, No. 4-6, 1996; 12040 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Volume 3, No. 1-2, 1996; 12041 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Volume 3, No. 3-4, 1997; 12042 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Volume 3, No. 5-6, 1997; 12043 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Volume 4, No. 1-2, 1997; 12044 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Volume 4, No. 3-4, 1998; 12045 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Volume 5, No. 1-2, 1998; 12046 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Volume 5, No. 3; Volume 6, No. 1, 1999; 12047 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Summer 2004, 12048 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Fall 2004, 12049 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Series VI: Golana, 11807
  Golana was a science fiction magazine produced by the students of Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. The magazine included original artwork, fiction, and poetry.
  - Volume 1, No. 1, 1963 December; 12050 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Undated, circa 1969; 12051 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - December/January 1965/66, 1965-1966; 12074 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Winter 1966, 12075 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fall 1967, 12076 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Spring 1968, 12077 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Spring 1969, 12078 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Spring 1970, 12079 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Spring 1971, 12080 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Series VII: Imaging Quarterly, 11810
  Imaging Quarterly was a publication of the newly formed Institute of Imaging Sciences at the Polytechnic Institute of New York.
  - Summer 1982 - Fall/Winter 1982, 12081 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Spring/Summer 1983 - Fall 1983, 12082 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Winter 1984, Summer/Fall 1984, Spring 1984, 12083 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Winter 1985, Fall/Winter 1985, Spring/Summer 1985, 12084 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Series VIII: News @ Poly, 11834
  News @ Poly was a publication of the Polytechnic University Public Affairs Department.
  - Volume 1, No. 1-2, 1995; 12085 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Volume 1, No. 3-4, 1996; 12086 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Volume 2, No. 1-2, 1996; 12087 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Volume 2, No. 3-4, 1997; 12088 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - November 1997, 12089 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - June 1998 - Winter 1998, 12090 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Spring 1999 - Winter 1999, 12091 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Spring 2000 - Fall 2000, 12092 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Spring 2001 - Winter 2001, 12093 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Series IX: Phoenix, 11835
  Phoenix was a literary magazine by and for Polytechnic students. The magazine included original poetry, prose, photographs, and drawings.
  - Winter 1977-1978, 12094 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Fall 1979, 12095 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Summer 1982, 12096 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Spring 1983, 12097 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Series X: Poly Men, 11836
  Poly Men was the former alumni publication of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Founded in 1921, the members of the Alumni Association unanimously agreed to adopt Trustee J. Monroe Hewlett's suggestion of "Poly Men" as the publication's name. Poly Men was later superceded by Polygraphs (1970 - 1979) and Cable Magazine (1973 - present).
  Arrangement
  The series is arranged chronologically by format, with bound volumes following loose issues in boxes and folders.
  - Volume 1, No. 1-3, 1921-1922; 12098 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Volume 2, No. 1-2, 1922-1923; 12099 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Volume 2, No. 1-3, 1924-1925; 12100 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents
    Not duplicates; numbering repeats with new content.
  - Volume 3, No. 1, 3, 4, 1927; 12101 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Volume 4, No. 1-5, 1928; 12102 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Volume 5, No. 1, 3-6, 1929; 12103 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Volume 6, No. 1-5, 1930; 12104 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Volume 6, No. 6-8, 1930; 12105 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Volume 7, No. 1-2, 1931; 12106 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Volume 9, No. 3; Volume 11, No.2, 1932-1934; 12107 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Volume 16, No. 1; Volume 22, No. 4, 1939, 1946; 12108 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Volume 29, No. 1, 3, 1952-1953; 12109 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Volume 30, No. 1-4, 1953-1954; 12110 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Volume 31, No. 1-3, 5, 1954-1955; 12111 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Volume 32, No. 1-5, 1956; 12112 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Volume 33, No. 1-5, 1957; 12113 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Volume 34, No. 1-5, 1958; 12114 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Volume 35, No. 1-5, 1959; 12115 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Volume 36, No. 1-4, 1960; 12116 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Volume 37, No. 1-4, 1961; 12117 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Volume 38, No. 2-4, 1962; 12118 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Volume 39, No. 2-4, 1963; 12119 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Volume 40, No. 1-4, 1964-1965; 12120 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Volume 41, No. 2-5, 1965; 12121 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Volume 41, No. 4-5, 1966; 12122 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Volume 42, No. 1-2, 1966; 12123 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Volume 42, No. 4-5, 1967; 12124 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Volume 43, No. 1-2, 1967; 12125 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Volume 43, No. 3, 5, 1968; 12126 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Volume 44, No. 2, 1968; 12127 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Volume 44, No. 4-5, 1969; 12128 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Volume 45, No. 1-2, 1969-1970; 12129 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Poly Men Newsletter 1954, 12534 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Poly Men Newsletter 1955-1956, 12535 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Poly Men Newsletter 1957, 12536 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Poly Men Newsletter 1960, 12537 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Poly Men Newsletter 1961, 12538 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Index A-Le, undated; 12130 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - Index Li - Z, undated; 12131 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - Volume 3-4 (bound), 1927-1928; 12220 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 1)
  - Volume 5-9 (bound), 1929-1933; 12221 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 2)
  - Volume 23-26 (bound), 1947-1949; 12222 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 3)
  - Volume 23-28 (bound), 1946-1952; 12223 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 4)
  - Volume 26-30 (bound), 1950-1953; 12224 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 5)
  - Volume 30-32 (bound), 1954-1955; 12225 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 6)
  - Volume 31-34 (bound), 1955-1958; 12226 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 7)
  - Volume 35-37 (bound), 1959-1961; 12227 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 8)
  - Volume 38 (bound), 1962; 12228 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 9)
  - Volume 38-40 (bound), 1962-1965; 12229 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 10)
  - Volume 39 (bound), 1963; 12230 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 11)
  - Volume 41-42 (bound), 1965-1967; 12231 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 12)
  - Volume 43-45 (bound), 1967-1970; 12232 (Item Shelf 36/4E, Item 13)
- Series XI: Poly Tatler, 11838
  The Poly Tatler was a periodical of campus news, letters, editorials, and fiction.
  - Volume I, 1908; 12233 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Item 1)
  - Volume II, 1909; 12234 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Item 2)
  - Volume III, 1909-1910; 12235 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Item 3)
  - Index, undated; 12236 (Item Shelf 37/2F, Item 4)
- Series XII: Polygraphs, 12132
  This series is arranged by complete issues and then notes/documentation corresponding to these issues.
  Polygraphs (1970-1979) was an alumni newsletter produced by the Brooklyn Polytechnic Alumni Association.
  - Volume 1, No. 1, 1970; 12133 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Volume 1, No. 2-3, 1971; 12134 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Volume 1, No. 4; Volume 2, No. 1, 1971; 12135 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Volume 2, No. 2; Volume 3, No. 1, 1972; 12136 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Volume 3, No. 2-3, 1972-1973; 12137 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Volume 4, No. 1, 1973; 12138 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Volume 4, No. 2, 1973-1974; 12139 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Volume 4, No. 3, 1974; 12140 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Volume 1, No. 1 (Long Island Edition), 1985 Spring; 12141 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1974-1981; 12142 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Poly Cable correspondence/documentation, 1976 July; 12143 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Poly Cable correspondence/documentation, 1977 May; 12144 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1977 November; 12145 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1978 June; 12146 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1978 February; 12147 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/photographs, 1978-1979; 12148 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Polygraphs & Poly Cable correspondence/documents/photographs, 1979; 12149 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1979 February; 12150 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1979 May; 12151 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Poly Cable photographs, 1979 September; 12152 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1980 May; 12153 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1980 December; 12154 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Polygraphs & Poly Cable documentation/photographs, 1981 March; 12155 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/photographs, 1981 June; 12156 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Polygraphs documentation/photographs, 1981 September; 12157 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1981-1984; 12158 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Polygraphs documentation/photographs, 1982 Winter; 12159 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Polygraphs documentation/photographs, 1982 Spring; 12160 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Polygraphs correspondence/documentation, 1983 Winter/Spring; 12161 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Polygraphs photographs, circa 1982; 12162 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Polygraphs & Poly Cable correspondence/documents, 1983 Summer; 12163 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Polygraphs & Poly Cable correspondence/documentation, 1983 Summer; 12164 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Polygraphs & Poly Cable photographs, undated; 12165 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Series XIII: Polytechnic Engineer, 11840
  The Polytechnic Engineer was a technical magazine, founded in 1898, for undergraduate students at Polytechnic. The magazine included student articles on engineering and science as well as current research at the school. The publication lay dormant for forty years, when it was resurrected in 1960 with a new volume 1.
  - Volume I, No. 1, 1960 Februrary; 12166 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Volume VIII, No. 1, 1966 October; 12167 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Volume XIII, No. 1, 1971 December; 12168 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Volume XIII, No. 2, 1972 Spring; 12169 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Volume XIV, No. 1, 1972 Fall; 12170 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Volume XIV, No. 2, 1973 Spring; 12171 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Volume XV, No. 1, 1973 Fall; 12172 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Volume XV, No. 2, 1974 Spring; 12173 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Volume XVI, No. 1, 1974 Fall; 12174 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Volume XVI, No. 2, 1975 February; 12175 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Volume XVI, No. 3, 1975 April; 12176 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Volume XVI, No. 4, 1975 November; 12177 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Volume XVII, No. 2, 1976 February; 12178 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Volume XVII, No. 1, 1977 November; 12179 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Survey of Engineering College Student Magazines- referencing Polytechnic Engineering, 1967 October; 12180 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Volume III (bound), 1900-1901; 12237 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 1)
  - Volume IV (bound), 1901-1902; 12238 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 2)
  - Volume V (bound), 1902-1903; 12239 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 3)
  - Volume VI (bound), 1903-1904; 12240 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 4)
  - Volume VII (bound), 1904-1905; 12241 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 5)
  - Volume VIII (bound), 1905-1906; 12242 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 6)
  - Volume IX (bound), 1906-1907; 12243 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 7)
  - Volume X (bound), 1910; 12244 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 8)
  - Volume XI (bound), 1911; 12245 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 9)
  - Volume XII (bound), 1912; 12246 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 10)
  - Volume XIII (bound), 1913; 12247 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 11)
  - Volume XIV (bound), 1914; 12248 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 12)
  - Volume XV (bound), 1915; 12249 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 13)
  - Volume XVI (bound), 1916; 12250 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 14)
  - Volume XVII (bound), 1917; 12251 (Item Shelf 36/2E, Item 15)
  - Volume 1-3 (bound), 1960-1962; 12252 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 16)
  - Volume 1-4 (bound), 1960-1963; 12253 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 17)
  - Volume 4 (bound), 1962-1963; 12254 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 18)
  - Volume 5 (bound), 1963-1964; 12255 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 19)
  - Volume 6 (bound), 1964-1965; 12256 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 20)
  - Volume 7 (bound), 1965-1966; 12257 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 21)
  - Volume 8 (bound), 1966-1967; 12258 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 22)
  - Volume 8 - 9 (bound), 1966-1968; 12259 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 23)
  - Volume 9 (bound), 1967-1968; 12260 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 24)
  - Volume 10 (bound), 1968-1969; 12261 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 25)
  - Volume 11 (bound), 1969-1970; 12262 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 26)
  - Index 1898 - 1968 (binder), undated; 12263 (Item Shelf 36/3E, Item 27)
- Series XIV: Polytechnic News, 11809